<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-16T06:18:11.448Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-04-16T06:18:11.448Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  April 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1930</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-april-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T01:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Mainnet execution layer Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko & Christine Kim: Keep shadow forking until no client issues, then upgrade Ropsten, followed by shorter timeframe for Goerli & Sepolia Rinkeby won’t be upgraded; Ropsten & Rinkeby will be deprecated latestValidHash analysis with potential attack scenarios EOF, SELFDESTRUCT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  April 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1928</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-april-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T03:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Mainnet execution layer Erigon stabilizing alpha version with merge support, full sync required as DB layout not compatible with beta version Verkle tree Condrieu testnet relaunched twice for continued stress-testing Predicting access lists to reduce state retrieval time for Portal network clients  Proof of Stake consensus layer PoS implementers call video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  April 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1926</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-april-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T03:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Mainnet execution layer Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko & Christine Kim: shadow fork merge testing finds RAM & timeout issues  difficulty bomb will need to be delayed if public testnet upgrades to PoS are not started by late April Shanghai upgrade planning: append withdrawals in block headers,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  March 26, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1920</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-march-26-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T03:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Mainnet execution layer Tim Beiko’s core devs update: merge testing, difficulty bomb can be pushed back as needed, Shanghai update proposed features, executable spec for execution layer and token compensation for client devs & researchers ethereumjs/client v0.4.0: Kiln v2 support Proof of Stake consensus layer Danny Ryan’s Finalized PoS update: help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  March 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1917</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-march-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-19T02:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Mainnet execution layer Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko: Kiln testnet transition to PoS successful, some implementation issues, more testing needed including devnets and live network shadow forks EIP4895 push withdrawals as operations selected for Shanghai EIP4844 data blob transaction type update Proposal to harmonize Core EIP process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>