<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-24T06:19:09.944Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-07-24T06:19:09.944Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  July 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1981</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-july-23-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-23T01:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links PoW switch off (the Merge) Goerli is the final testnet to merge before mainnet, TTD expected August 9-11 Goerli-shadow-fork-5 merged successfully Mainnet-shadow-fork-10 merges July 28 Mainnet execution layer Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko and Christine Kim: Node operators need to run both execution & consensus layer clients]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  July 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1979</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-july-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T00:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links PoW switch off (the Merge) Tentative Merge timeline to turn off PoW in mid to late September:  Goerli testnet August 11 Pick mainnet TTD in mid-August assuming Goerli successfully merges Mainnet merge lightly penciled in for week of September 19 PoS implementers call video. Notes from Ben Edgington and Christine Kim:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  July 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1976</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-july-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T00:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links PoW switch off (the Merge) Sepolia testnet merged successfully: TTD config issue specific to PoW testnets Mainnet-shadow-fork-8 merged successfully Mainnet-shadow-fork-9 merges July 14, plan to test MEV-boost Mainnet execution layer Tim Beiko’s core devs update: stakers prepare for merge, block times back to ~13s after Gray Glacier upgrade, testnets being deprecated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  July 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1974</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-july-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-02T02:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links PoW switch off (the Merge) The second of three public testnets to merge will occur next week, with Sepolia to turn off PoW forever sometime between Saturday and Wednesday, depending on hashpower Mainnet-shadow-fork-8 merges July 5 Mainnet execution layer Gray Glacier upgrade (delay difficulty bomb) successful; One block on wrong chain,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  June 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=1972</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-june-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-06-25T01:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links PoW switch off (the Merge) Mainnet-shadow-fork-7 merged with caveats: known Besu concurrency issue and Erigon issue with shadow forks Mainnet execution layer Update your nodes for Gray Glacier upgrade Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko and Christine Kim: Sepolia testnet merge planned for July 6 Mainnet shadow fork]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>