<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-12-02T06:17:50.841Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-12-02T06:17:50.841Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  November 26, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=2041</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-november-26-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-26T00:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Layer 1 Latest core devs call video. Notes from Tim Beiko: March 2023 semi-aggressive goal for next fork (“Shanghai”) with staking withdrawals (EIP4895) along with EIP3651 (warm COINBASE), EIP3855 (PUSH0) & EIP3860 (limit & meter initcode) Possible additional EIPs for Shanghai to be finalized at next core devs call; impact of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  November 19, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=2038</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-november-19-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T01:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Layer 1 EIP4844 (proto-danksharding) readiness checklist EVM Object Format (EOF) EIPs explainer Latest consensus layer call video. Notes from Ben Edgington & Christine Kim: MEV-Boost update: Flashbots no longer top builder   Withdrawals: discussion on setting a bound to avoid sweeping the entire validator set EIP4844 blobs to be verified, will check]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  November 12, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=2036</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-november-12-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T03:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Layer 1 Latest core devs call video. Notes from Christine Kim: Shanghai upgrade planning, EIPs jostling to potentially be included along with withdrawals: EOF, EIP4844 (proto-danksharding), EIP4758 (deactivate SELFDESTRUCT), EIP1153 (transient storage) & EIP2537 (BLS12 precompile) Next call to focus on triage of Shanghai upgrade EIPs Users of SELFDESTRUCT need to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week in Ethereum News  November 5, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://weekinethereumnews.com/?p=2031</id>
        <link href="https://weekinethereumnews.com/week-in-ethereum-news-november-5-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-05T01:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eth News and Links Layer 1 Latest consensus layer call video. Notes from Ben Edgington & Christine Kim: Full & partial withdrawals to be processed in a single queue-less pipeline EIP4844 (proto-danksharding) to be developed on top of withdrawals Block value to be added to EngineAPI to allow comparing MEV-Boost vs locally built blocks MEV-Boost]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Coathup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>